Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during
the filming of this series.
Bursa Palace
We'll fight.
We can't lose to
the Turks anymore.
We have to do something.
How could you lose Kopruhisar?
Do the Byzantine soldiers carry
their swords only to show off?
If people are led by others who don't
know how to fight instead of commanders...
...the inevitable ending is near.
But first of all, the commander
needs to know his place.
Are Lords talking now,
who couldn’t protect their people?
You have commanders who
have seen dozens of battles.
Lords don't need to be afraid of us.
Those who should be afraid are the Turks.
You were there when our armies
set their tribes on fire, Commander Mateus.
We stopped the help Lord
Valens sent from Konya, too.
How could Osman do that?
You underestimated Osman...
...and the price for it was Kopruhisar.
Osman has the Lord of Kopruhisar.
No, Lord.
Osman does not have
Petrus, Lord of Kopruhisar...
but I do.
Leo.
Look what those Turks did to us.
Anyone that sleeps before we
take the revenge for this...
...will lose their eyes...
...my friends.
Those who dream of taking revenge on us
will beg for forgiveness when they wake up.
Or when they wake up to our
swords on their necks.
The sleep of a fool is deep, brother.
No one expected that we
would conquer Kopruhisar.
Kopruhisar's conquests will be a
symbol of our victory always.
Osman Bey, what's your next goal?
It looks like your soldiers
are turning this into a race.
Is that so?
My sons.
So, you are curious about my plans.
Tell me.
Where will we go next?
We both have different ideas, father.
Tell us our destination, so we
can determine the winner.
My brothers, protect the Princes.
Stop.
Wait.
If this arrow...
...belonged to our enemies...
...then...
...it would strike us instead
of the ground.
My sons, until I return, think
about where I will go next.
Let's see who will be the winner.
Boran Alp.
Where are they taking my father?
I know many secrets of my Bey, Orhan Bey.
But this is not one of them.
Father said that they are
allies, but who are they?
Osman crossed the Iine.
Kopruhisar, conquered by Osman, is
sacred for us, Lord Valens.
Did you send your letters?
Lord Valens.
My cousin in Teselya established
an army of barbarians.
They are coming.
What about you, Commander Seth?
My friends in Vidin answered my letter.
The armies are established, Lord
Valens, they^re coming to feed with blood.
Good.
Even if we burn down Osman's tribe..
...even if we stop the help
coming to him...
...we know that he won't stop.
The only way to stop him...
...is to cut off his head.
We will do that.
We will establish a base in Kartalgozu to
welcome the armies.
This duty is yours.
What will Osman's next target be?
If we know that, it will be
easy to cut off his head.
I'm listening.
If he moves towards
Kestel Castle...
...it'll be the end of him.
My soldiers are waiting in Lefke.
Byzantine’s great commanders.
What will Osman's next target be?
When I look at Osman's
previous conquests...
..the map shows that..
...he wants to cut contact
between Marmara and Bursa.
You're a real soldier.
Kopruhisar...
...is where he gets closer to his goal.
He wants to do this and rid
Anatolia of the Byzantines.
That's why his next goal...
...will be Koyunhisar.
If he takes control of it...
...İznik and Bursa will lose contact.
Byzantine’s great commanders...
and Lords...
You will take precaution in your castles.
Council brothers.
Gather all of your soldiers.
Commander Milos.
Commander Seth.
When the armies arrive..
...not a single Turk will
breathe in this land.
It's not enough to make an agreement.
We'll swear on Jesus Christ.
Priest.
Until we rest under the flag
of Jesus Christ.
We'll burn the infidels with the God’s sun.
Until heaven is ours.
Until heaven is ours,
We'll make them go through hell.
This is our oath.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Have a seat, Osman Bey.
Congratulations on the Kopruhisar
conquest, Osman Bey.
Thanks.
Thanks to you...
...we knew the location of all passages.
Thank you.
Where's your next target, Osman Bey?
Our target will aIways be Red Apple.
But...
...our short term goal...
...is for Byzantines...
..to leave the board.
It will be a tough battle.
We never deal with with the easy way.
Let Byzantines send an army.
We'll kill them all with our steel hands.
They'll never stop Osman Bey.
This is a war between right and wrong.
They'll never stop even if you do.
But...
...you can never make
peace with superstitious beliefs.
Stopping on the other hand..
...will only send us back.
Now tell me.
Let us know what you know.
Who is coming?
Lord Valens...
...has called for everyone who is
capable of holding a sword under his rule.
Especially...
...two cruel commanders.
His hands are covered with thousands
of brave men’s blood.
We'll cut off those
hands covered in blood.
But...
...if you tell me to behead
those who are..
...leading the army...
...that's okay too.
Commanders are fine.
What about the others?
Men from Lord's own team.
Those in the council are
always hidden as a precaution.
But...
...you're the ones who
keep secrets within secrets.
There's no one who's
better at hiding than you.
Tell me.
How can they hide from you?
There's no hidden or clear, Osman Bey.
There's no politics now.
There will be a war now.
Without the armies.
Without the big alliance being made.
So, you're saying it’s hunting season, huh?
For Gokboru, it is time to hunt.
We will drown those who are...
...coming to kill us in their own blood.
I will hunt Valens and those who stand with him...
down one by one.
And Koyunhisar...
...will be my hunting ground.
Don't worry.
I'm going to end them all.
Thank you.
- Thanks, Osman Bey.
- Thanks.
The dark midwife?
Alcicek, good news.
You're pregnant.
Are you serious, dark midwife?
Am I going to be a mother now?
Yes.
And Aktemur, a father?
Inshallah.
Mashallah, Alcicek.
When Aktemur hears about this...
Allah...
I hope this is good news, Inshallah.
Alcicek, are you okay?
It is good news Malhun Hatun, it is.
Alcicek is pregnant.
The babies are coming one
after the other thank Allah.
Alcicek, I'm so happy to hear that.
May Allah allow you
to hold them in your arms.
- Amin.
- Amin, Inshallah.
Thank you.
I need to go to the tribe now.
They are waiting for material for the burnt tents.
And I need to give the good news
to Aktemur and my mother.
Of course.
But you can't go alone.
I'll send a few Alps with you.
No need, aunt Malhun.
Alps are waiting for me in the field.
It's okay to be safe.
Gorkluce.
My sons.
Alps.
It's time for us to begin the conquest.
Our target is Koyunhisar.
Kopruhisar gave us
control over the Iznik road.
Inshallah, the conquest of Koyunhisar, will
give us control over Bursa road.
Inshallah.
Inshallah, my Bey, but we could have
sent spies there if you told us.
Where is our spy, Aktemur?
He might be here any minute, my Bey.
I told Aktemur once...
...and we had a spy in Koyunhisar
the whole time.
My Bey.
Have you been planning
to get Koyunhisar...
...before even getting
Kopruhisar, my Bey?
If you knew about the things I
planned and dreamt of...
...you would never be able
to sleep at night.
Thanks.
Tell me, Kutlu.
They're happy after the damage
we suffered, my Bey.
They were planning to have fun...
...but Kopruhisar’s
conquest destroyed them.
They moved all soldiers in nearby
castles and villages to Koyunhisar.
Lord must have arrived to Bursa.
They're waiting for us, my Bey.
Here are the maps, my Bey.
Let them wait.
They will be afraid.
They won't even be able to sleep at night;
They will be destroyed...
...and when they’re least expecting it...
..Koyunhisar will become a property of Turks.
But there's something else
we have to do before.
Some of them want to unite and kill us.
We'll march on them first.
My Bey.
We have news from our scouts.
Esrigun Hatun is going to Yenisehir.
Alps.
We're going to Yenisehir.
May it be easy.
- May it be easy.
- Thanks.
- May I?
- It's halal, go ahead.
- May it be easy.
- Thank you. Welcome.
Thank you.
It's silk, huh?
- Is it good?
- It's the best.
Thanks to Osman Bey, all goods
in Yenisehir are good.
So, Osman Bey is taking good care of you.
How are the merchants doing?
He does not stop fighting, and he
always keeps our well-being in his mind.
He always protects us.
He protects the merchants, may
Allah bless Osman Bey.
You keep complimenting him, but...
- that's not what I've heard.
- What did you hear, Hatun?
Tell me, what did you hear about Osman Bey?
I heard that he is a dreamer.
He dreams things that are beyond him.
It looks like you've
heard these from the enemy.
Don't believe everything you hear.
Is what I heard a lie, Hatun?
Isn't Osman Bey putting a heavy
burden upon his people with his dreams?
What is the dream that
becomes a burden to the people?
The rebel called Nayman on one hand
and Bursa Lord on the other.
And there is also Konya.
You lose everyday.
You are bleeding, but you keep fighting.
You are crossing the line, Hatun.
Your ignorance must be leading
you talk bravely like this.
I don't know where you are coming
from, but these are the borderlands.
Wherever you go, you face
an enemy in these lands!
You will learn where my bravery comes
from when we are introduced.
You are Esrigun hatun.
You must be Malhun Hatun.
Then what are you doing here? We
were waiting for you at the mansion.
I wanted to learn about the
people’s opinion on Osman Bey.
As you know...
...you are bound to Seljuk state...
...and Seljuk state is bound to us.
Sultan Alaeddin's secret house.
Celali.
Send messengers all around Seljuk state.
I will take my throne back!
I want soldiers loyal to me behind me!
Your command, my Sultan.
When our soldiers arrive
at the borderlands...
..we will take revenge from
those who dethroned you!
I swear that we will kill all of them!
Those who lived with my mercy...
...will soon live with my wrath.
I will ask soldiers from Lord
and Nayman for the army we will gather.
Lord pledged his friendship to Sultan Mesut.
And Nayman will support him.
We will build our victory with
our own hands, my Sultan!
Then, the rebellious borderlands...
...and Osman will be killed by us!
No children of Osman will...
...sit on the throne, and they will not have a future!
But first...
...I will punish these traitors.
Bengi and Alcicek survived the
attack on the tribe.
Karabul is after them.
When he brings Alcicek...
...I will punish Bengi and Alcicek...
..with my own hands.
Mother Sultan wants her alive.
Alps! It's a trap!
Alps! Protect Alcicek Hatun!
Come on!
Attack!
No way out.
Mother Sultan is waiting for you.
Your mother and you will
pay for your treason.
There's no way out.
Surrender.
You're the traitor.
Ismihan is the traitor.
Both you and you mother will die.
Hurry! Follow her!
Osman Bey, welcome.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
May Allah protect you, my Bey.
Long live, Osman Bey
This way!
Follow her.
Come on.
Hurry! Come on.
Over here!
Come on.
She went this way.
She's injured.
She couldn’t have made it far.
My baby.
She got away.
We're going back.
We'll go by the riverbed.
She is not here.
We're going back.
What will we tell Mother Sultan now?
She's injured.
She won't make it alive
out of here.
Come on.
They took Alcicek Hatun.
Alps...
Gather around.
Leave no trace behind.
Bring my horse.
I'm going to let Mother Sultan know.
Welcome to our mansion, Esrigun Hatun.
If you are our guest
until we get Ismihan...
..then, you will be hosted
without any mistakes.
They prison us between stone walls.
You must have fallen for that as well...
..and abandoned your tents.
Do you think sycamores forget
about their roots...
...as they grow
towards the sky, Hatun?
I don't know about you...
...but both our mansions and tents...
...are filled with hearts
beating for the Word of Allah.
Is that a girl?
She's pretty, too.
Although Turkmens live in separated locations...
...their cause is the same.
Do you think Cerkutay knows her?
That's the difference between
Turkmens and us.
We conquer more lands while
you only dream about it.
Well...
...if we only spoke and
didn’t take any action...
...you wouldn't be
here now, Esrigun Hatun.
You must be aware of the struggle
you went through so I’d be here...
..and what would have happened if I
refused to do so, Osman Bey.
You're right.
You're right, thank you.
You helped us make it out of the trap
that they had set.
Thank you.
Sultan Mesut is on the throne.
Muslims are brothers
and that’s what happened.
We will do our part, as it needed.
If we don't kill and die for
the world of Islam...
...the blood Nayman spilled
will stain the flag of Tabriz.
Both you and Gazhan Khan
are aware of that.
Anyway, we can talk about it later.
Prepare a nice dinner tonight so that we can share...
...our bread...
...our problems...
...and our call with our guest.
To share a call, you must first
share bread, Osman Bey.
I'd be glad.
Thanks.
Aktemur...
...you should stay, as well.
Tell the Alps to bring Alcicek here.
We'll recover from this, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Bengi Hatun.
Bengi Hatun...
...Osman Bey disregarded your
exile sentence.
Thanks.
But no crime should go unpunished.
I'll gladly accept any punishment
once my tribe is doing better.
The supply needed for the tents
haven't arrived yet.
What should we do?
Alcicek is late.
She knew that we wee in a hurry.
Aybars, send an Alp.
Are you okay?
Get the healer here.
What happened?
Who did this to you?
Bengi Hatun.
Bengi Hatun...
Alcicek Hatun was kidnapped.
By whom?
The Mother...
They mentioned the Mother Sultan.
Ismihan...
Alcicek!
Calm down, Bengi Hatun.
Don't think of bad things!
We will find Alcicek.
Alps! Bring the spies!
Make preparations, we will
go to Yenisehir, come on;
Call the healer!
Come on.
Sultan Alaeddin's secret house.
Alcicek.
Where is she?
I was about to capture her...
You were about to capture her?
This bloodied cape and
her sword.
I lost her track in the forest.
It is impossible for her to survive.
She is wounded.
You couldn't do one thing!
What will we do now, madam?
Did anyone see Alcicek?
No.
She was distant from the Alps.
We cleaned the tracks and
removed the dead bodies.
Then, we will continue our plan.
Since no one has seen Alcicek..
...then they won’t be
able to find her corpse.
They will think that I have Alcicek.
We will send word to Bengi, if she
does not come to where we want...
...she will be sure that
I will kill her daughter.
What if she does not come, madam?
Motherhood...
...can bury you alive.
When Bengi sees that her daughter's
scent is mixed with blood...
..she will come to me.
Yenisehir, Osman Bey's mansion.
What are they talking about?
I don't know.
They are whispering.
Gurbuz.
Alp...
So, you are here, huh, Cerkutay Alp?
Gurbuz Alp told me everything one by one.
What did he tell you?
What did you tell her?
Well, I told her everything.
You must be really brave, Cerkutay..
You are brave enough to ask for
her hand in marriage.
What are you saying, mother?
Shut up!
We will talk later.
Cerkutay, so, you are..
...in love with my...
...daughter, huh?
I won't let my daughter
marry a crazy person.
I said what I said but...
...Gurbuz Alp said...
..."he is smart."
He said, "That's why he seems crazy."
You're a good swordsman.
I asked around about you.
There is no better son in law than you.
But...
...I have 3 conditions.
I accept them.
Wait!
Listen.
When you marry my girl...
Yes.
Where will you live?
The mansion.
No.
First, I want a house!
Of course.
We'll get a house, Cerkutay.
You'll pay mahr which will be...
...Ulgen's weight in gold.
Of course.
We'll get it, right, Cerkutay?
I want...
the biggest greatest gift.
It will be this height.
Of course.
We'll get it, right, Cerkutay?
Yes.
Find those first.
Then come and ask for my
daughter's hand in marriage.
Off you go.
Go on.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Let's go.
Let’s go.
Mother.
Why didn't you ask for more?
Ask him to give us Yenisehir.
Or better yet, ask to have the
city where it all started.
Maybe, Inegol?
Ulgen.
How can he find all of that?
Ulgen!
I have just one daughter.
It's not easy to marry my
daughter.
He must do it.
Mother.
Aunt.
Alcicek's not here.
Did you hear from her?
No, son.
We have
sent a messenger but he hasn’t arrived.
I'm worried too.
Where are you, Alcicek?
She said she had good news.
What?
It's good news, Ayse, but...
..it’s a secret for now.
Attention!
Osman Bey is coming!
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam, my Bey.
Have a seat.
"In the name of Allah, the Most
Gracious, the Most Merciful."
Go ahead.
Enjoy your meal.
You accepted our invite.
Thank you.
We shared our bread.
And now it's time to...
...share our worries and call.
So......
40 foxes...
...walk around these borders...
...and every one of their tails
touch one and another.
We try to solve the problems
caused by this.
I see it, Osman
Bey, I see it.
And the biggest fox is Lord Valens.
He thinks that he can move
every stone on these lands...
...since he went to visit Sultan
Mesut when he was crowned.
I know that.
I know.
He sent his regards.
Lord Valens...
..eats with the wolf...
...and cries with the shepherd.
That's his nature.
He always talks behind people’s back.
That's why he has a
lot of people with him.
He has a lot of allies.
Even...
...he has many people who
would die for him.
As long as Nayman with the Lord...
...it's hard to defeat
them both.
Wherever the Lord stands...
I will cut that traitor
Nayman’s liver off of his body.
We will take the mountains Lord
Valens gets support from.
After we leave him without power...
...Nayman will fall into our hands.
What do you have in mind, Osman Bey?
You will learn about it like
everyone else, Esrigun Hatun.
We saved his life but he doesn't trust us.
Don t take it personally, Esrigun
Hatun but a Bey's business is secret.
Thanks.
Thanks, Osman Bey.
Mashallah.
It can be seen that you raised your
sons for the world of Islam.
Someone who is no stranger to our
language has a place in our hearts.
The wind and the storm of the Islam world...
..will never end.
But the enemies...
...think that the storm will put out our fire.
But...
...it only strengthens us.
So...
..a seed of the flower which
grows on these lands....
...will travel all over the world.
And that's what unites us.
To unite..
...we need to know each other well.
We need to get to know each other well.
And our sons...
...were brought up with the same idea.
They were taught by my Sheykh Edebali....
...and now...
...they're entrusted to Kumral AbdaI.
Thank Allah...
...Allah gifted me with this mission.
Our only worry and mission..
...is to hold on to the rope of Allah.
And raise our children to do so too.
What does it say in the verse of the Quran?
"And hold firmly to the rope of Allah..
...all together and do not become divided."
[3:103]
Whenever I hear this,
it shakes me Kumral Abdal
What do we take from it?
Allah says that...
...Allah's rope is a rope hanging down
from the sky down to earth.
Of course we can not look for this rope with our eyes.
We can see it with the eyes of our hearts.
We know that this rope...
...is Quran and Islam.
It's the mission of Islam.
Why are we still waiting, mother?
Every minute spent here is wasted.
We're supposed to prepare an army
but you're messing with Bengi.
The Mother Sultan of Seljuk...
...does not leave any unfinished business.
She never forgives a
pawn like Bengi.
I will take back everything...
...that they stole from us.
But I’ll get my revenge first.
Bengi will scream in pain.
I will watch her die.
The end I have prepared for her..
...will be spoken about for centuries.
Mother...
...your ambition is going to get us in trouble.
Ambition isn’t the reason, justice is!
No one can cross me!
and those who do pay for it!
You'll see.
Everyone will see!
Just like how the stars are scattered
throughout the sky...
...Muslims are scattered on the earth as well.
It's not good when Muslims stay
that way like the stars do.
When separated, Muslims can't overcome
the darkness of the infidels.
Separation is a Muslim's test.
Quran is the most important guide...
...Allah sent to help us get through the test.
For that reason, Muslims shall
embrace the Great Quran together...
..so that Allah's mercy..
...can hug people.
You spoke well, Kumral Abdal..
..but even Muslims have nafs.
Even though everything belongs to Allah,
they’re in a race to see who has more...
...and since that's the case,
it's difficult to stay in Allah’s path...
...after joining such a race.
He says that "Surely the most noble of you in the sight
of Allah is the most righteous among you" [49:13]
Those who are already in Allah's path...
..shall overcome the test.
They become a whole.
They know that Islam is above
all races and all languages.
Hearts that beat to spread
the Religion of Allah are one.
Of course there will be hypocrites among you.
There will be those who claim
that they share our cause but betray us.
But Muslims protect and
stay true to each other.
We will not let our guards down
against those...
...who are waiting with daggers in their hands.
May Allah allow us to remain united
against such hypocrites...
...and remain strong.
I hope you're among those
who stay true to each other, Osman Bey.
For sure, Esrigun Hatun.
We're true to both our enemies and friends.
I see that's the case for you as well.
May Allah keep you in his path.
Amen.
Osman!
Aktemur!
Bala!
Osman!
What's wrong?
Tell me what happened.
Mother... Where's Alcicek?
Alcicek’ Ismihan kidnapped Alcicek.
What?
Mother’? Aunt?
How could this happen?
Alcicek?
Alcicek is pregnant.
She was going to give you the good news.
Pregnant?
Mother?
Am I going to be a father?
How was she kidnapped?
We checked everywhere,
there are no traces.
We searched everywhere from the tribe to Yenisehir,
there is no trace of alps or Alcicek.
The wounded alp that came here
became a martyr.
We couldn't learn where they were ambushed.
Alps!
You will search everywhere, come on!
We are going to the assembly now.
Don't worry.
We will find your child and Alcicek.
Come on.
Mother.
Mother, where are you?
Oh Allah, help!
Help me.
I told you to stay at the tribe,
why are you here, nephew?
Alps brought this.
It's for you.
It's personal, I wanted to bring it myself.
They said no one but Bengi hatun should open it.
If you want to see Alcicek alive,
come to Alatas, near Karaagac.
You will come alone.
If you tell anyone, you won't...
...you won't see your child again.
Ismihan!
What is this!?
Alcicek!
I will come.
I will save you my daughter.
I will not leave you her!
Be patient, daughter.
I will save you and my grandchild.
Aunt, this is a trap.
If you go there alone, Ismihan will kill you.
You will not say anything to anyone.
My daughter's and grandchild’s lives depend on it.
Never, Aybars!
Never.
The carriage left Yenisehir,
but there is no trace on the path.
They must have cleaned it after the ambush.
Ismihan wouldn't kidnap Alcicek without a reason.
She will want something for sure.
Boran.
My Bey.
Increase the number of Alps.
You will search everywhere in the borderlands!
As you command my Bey.
Cerkutay.
My Bey.
You will take scouting alps with you.
You will search everywhere from here to tribe.
As you command my Bey.
I have skilled scouts among my men.
We would like to do our part.
Thank you. Thank you.
May I come in?
Come in.
Bengi Hatun.
If Ismihan sends word to you..
...tell us right away.
What can she want from me?
She took my beloved one,
what more can she want?
They removed all tracks...
That means Alcicek is alive.
You're right but...
...Ismihan doesn't want us to find her.
She's up to something.
Don't worry.
I will tell you if something comes up.
But I have no hope.
Do not lose hope, Bengi
We'll find our daughter safe and sound
with Allah's help.
She has to be alive.
I know it.
I'll find them.
We'll take the groom and our nephew back.
We won’t leave them there.
Don't worry.
Everyone knows what to do.
I hope(if Allah permits)
we'll end this before sunrise.
Hang on.
Your father will save us.
Aktemur.
Where are you?
Calm down first.
How can I, mother?
If they hurt her...
They can't harm her.
They can't harm your child or Alcicek.
They’ll be just fine.
I'll break the hands that try to reach her!
She..
They...
...must be protected.
Son...
You entrusted them with Allah, son...
If Allah permits...
...Alcicek and our baby
will be okay, I hope.
Have patience.
Patience!!
I couldn't protect them mother.
I couldn't protect my tribe, my Hatun...
I couldn't even protect my unborn baby!
Aktemur...
Stop.
I will save you.
I'll burn the whole world..
..if I have to.
Wait for me Alcicek.
Wait.
Bursa Palace.
You've met him, you know him more or less.
How does he fight?
Who does he trust?
Or, does he trust anyone?
He trusts only his closest men.
What's his weakness?
Is his family more important...
or his people?
They are all the same for him, sir.
I have been kept captive there.
The merchant is right. That’s why he’s so strong.
And..
...justice, sir.
Justice?
He waited at my door for hours.
He didn’t get mad.
He didn't leave.
He just did what he had to.
He didn’t react to any provocation of me.
What is a shepherd who can do nothing
but serve in my kitchen...
...doing here in front of me?
He was patient.
He just said what he had.
And most importantly...
...he saw things we thought he didn't.
The archers.
But..
What if he realises again?
Who?
Who realises what, Lord Valens?
I'm going to gauge out those eyes
he sees with today, Nayman.
Let's leave.
I told you that we would behead them.
It's time now.
Who will we kill my Bey?
Lord Valens.
He's gathering people.
Even armies will come to support him
from west.
But the real power..
The real power is knowledge.
We know where they are and
the secrets of those who are hidden.
Are we going to kidnap them, my Bey?
We will take down the leader.
Now...
...they're forming a big army.
Even a huge army from the west is
coming to support them.
We will take down the ones whom he trusts the most,
and his commanders.
Cerkutay...
...Konur, Baysungur and Gurbuz.
You..
..will go to Kestel
Bayindir...
...Huseyin, Turhan and Aykut,
you will go to Lefke.
Everything is written in these.
These are all for precaution.
Who will go to take down the commanders
in the headquarters?
I will confront them.
Will you go alone, my Bey?
I mean,
will you take them down by yourself?
Foals grow up, horses get to rest...
...the son grows up, the Bey gets to rest.
Why are my sons here?
They practiced so much.
It's time to test them now.
What are you waiting for alps?
They will be tested against
the toughest opponents now...
...so that they can withstand even tougher ones.
My Bey.
What we need is this kind of experience.
Let us go through this and prove ourselves.
Is it easy to be a son of a Bey?
There's my boy.
Come on then.
Everyone back to their duty!
You shouldn't have come Aybars.
I told you to stay at the tribe.
I won't leave you alone aunt.
Put down your swords.
Are you afraid of two people?
Right, you're not brave enough to face us.
You sound too brave for a woman
whose daughter is missing, Bengi Hatun.
You're a coward, Ismihan
Enough to collaborate with your enemy...
...and take innocent lives
for your own benefit!
Enough!
You're not here to talk.
You're here to be punished.
Where's Alcicek?
My girl...
Alcicek!
Let Alcicek go, Ismihan.
You called me, here I am.
Let Alcicek go and kill me.
No.
It's not that easy.
Not that easy, Bengi Hatun.
You betrayed me!
You messed everything up!
My son lost the throne because of you!
I will take both of your lives, Bengi Hatun!
But first, I'll let you experience
the greatest pain in the world!
Kill her!
Alcicek!
Oh, Haqq!
In the name of Allah!
It's over, Ismihan!
Run, Alaeddin!
Run!
Like you said, Osman Bey...
Ismihan sent me a message.
She wants me in return for Alcicek's life.
It's a trap.
She won't spare you or Alcicek.
Once you're aware of the trap,
it becomes useless.
You'll go there, Bengi Hatu
What if they hurt Alcicek?
Ismihan is capable of anything.
We'll be careful.
MaIhun.
Bala.
Aktemur.
Make your preparations.
Be there before sunrise.
As you command.
Alaeddin is from us.
Let's go after him!
That's not Alcicek.
Alcicek?
You will never see your daughter again, Bengi.
Where is Alcicek?
She’s dead.
Speak!
Where is Alcicek’?
Alcicek is dead.
I took your daughter from you, Bengi.
Murderer!
Traitor!
Let go of me!
My daughter was pregnant!
Alcicek was pregnant! Let go of me!
She killed a young girl!
Bengi!
You did not kill her Ismihan.
If you wanted to kill her,
you would have done it in front of Bengi.
Now speak, where is Alcicek_
You know me very well.
I wanted to kill her in front of her mother.
But while my men were trying to capture her...
...they killed her.
So I killed two of you, huh?
But it's not enough.
I will kill you too, Bengi.
Ismihan!
Let go!
Bengi!
You damn devil!
Speak, which of your men did this!?
Where is Alcicek?
Get up! Speak!
Dead.
She is not dead!
But I will hear it from you!
Where is Alcicek?
Stop.
Don't.
I just followed the orders.
I did what Mother Sultan asked me.
Where is Alcicek?
We ambushed them.
She got away.
She's in the forest up ahead.
She's wounded.
I'll deal with her.
Find Alcicek. Go.
I'll make you pay for this when the time comes.
If Alcicek is hurt..
...then you'll pay for it.
Now shut up.
Or I'll cut off your tongue.
Mother.
Alaeddin.
Malhun Hatun.
Give Ismihan to us.
Only after Alcicek is found.
If Alcicek is hurt...
,,..no one can take this devil from us.
Alps!
We'll go back to Yenisehir.
Sons.
This is harder than a battle.
Sometimes, we need to be quiet.
We need to hide.
And we need to wear disguises.
But most importantly...
...we need to hide our daggers.
Orhan.
How many daggers do I have on me?
These two.
Alaeddin. Go ahead, son.
There was one more, huh?
Sons.
If the guards
where you're going are like you...
...how tough it is for those commanders!
Firstly...
...you check everywhere closely.
That's one.
And that's two.
And that's three.
What's important...
..is that you hide your swords and
daggers in the best way possible.
Right sons?
Sons.
The most important thing
is to be quite.
Even if you step on a branch,
that noise can be the end of you.
That's why you’ll be careful.
Okay?
Let's go now.
My sons.
So you separated into two wings...
...and surprised him from both sides...
...when he least expected it.
Good.
We did think
we could surprise him, my Bey.
Well done.
If one of us falls down,
the other can drive the dagger, my Bey.
Oi praise be! My Beys.
They’re clearly going to play
with the infidels, my Bey.
Of course.
They’ve been going through
their training for a reason.
Now the next one.
Come, Orhan.
Alaeddin.
My sons, I know you are skilled archers.
But that is different.
You will hit the small target away.
It may look easy, but it is not.
This is a sharp shoot. Now.
Orhan, move.
Closer.
Now, look at your target
and find yourself a gap.
Exactly.
Focus.
Breathe.
Now...
...you will look 5 span above your target.
When you are sure...
...hold your breath.
Shoot.
Alaeddin.
Your turn.
Closer. Closer.
Look at your target.
Look look look look.
Breathe in, move your elbow.
Now..
...hold your breath...
...and shoot.
Come here.
Praise be!
My sons, just as I said...
...you hit the target in the eye.
My Bey, we got word from alps,
they arrived.
Then we should strike at the same time.
Let's go quickly.
Come on my sons.
Kestel Church.
What's wrong my son?
I sinned, father.
Speak, my child,
that's why I am here.
But I have never seen you
at the church before.
I go from church to church...
...and search for a remedy for my soul.
But I can’t find it.
What blackens your soul like this?
I killed many men.
Christians.
God is forgiving.
If you did not enjoy....
...and if you regret it,
God will forgive you.
I enjoy cutting infidels, father.
Churches have always been graves for you!
Lord Valens said that you would come!
Attack!
You all want to kill me,
but none of you can!
Oh Allah!
They are coming!
I will come back.
They are running way!
Capture them!
Akte...
Aktemur..
Alps!
You will search the trunk of every tree!
No.
We'll find her.
No matter what, we'll find her!
Allah help us, my Creator.
Alcicek!
She’s alive.
She's alive. Mothers can feel it.
My girl's breathing.
Keep praying to Allah.
We'll find her.
Alcicek!
- Daughter, speak!
- Alcicek!
A rich and smart merchant..
...can find the best goods to buy.
But...
..there is one thing..
...you can't buy with money.
Yes.
And that is Yagiz slave.
I understand,
but a Turk can't be a slave.
Astagfirullah. Of course.
But we have to. That's the game.
Listen. You'll be a slave first.
Then we'll cut heads.
Bayindir Bey.
Why am the thief?
Why not something else?
This is just a game.
Just steal my pouch at the market.
He will run and catch you.
Then all the people will see
how strong and fast he is.
And then two merchants
will come to buy him from me.
And after that the biggest battle will begin.
Osman Bey gave me this duty.
Come on. Let's get back to duty.
Come on. In the name of Allah.
A rich merchant...
...gets the best goods.
Over there. Stop
I said stop!
There are so many thieves.
Our dear Lord in heaven.
Ever since you sank my ships
in the Red Sea...
...you've never answered my prayers.
My slave deserves every inch of
the gold I'll give him.
May God bless you.
Wait.
Don't.
The fear is a good punishment.
Let him be.
May God bless you.
My dear friend!
You are no slave, you’re a dear friend!
If I didn't have to, I'd never sell you!
But it's life.
Walk.
No one's coming Bayindir Bey.
They will. They will.
Merchants always follow a fallen seller.
They will come eventually.
We praised our slave and presented well.
It's a trap!
Now it's time...
...to shed some blood.
Run!
Father.
Is it you?
Mother.
This won't do.
The sun is about to set.
You’re right.
Alcicek.
If something happens to her...
It's not the time Bengi,
we can't lose hope.
We will find both of them safe.
We'll play with our grandkid, hold on.
If Allah permits...
If Allah permits, Ayse, if Allah permits.
Alcicek!
Let's separate!
You go that way and
we’ll go this way.
Come on alps!
Split up!
Forgive me, my child.
I failed to protect you.
Alcicek.
I'm going to find you
no matter what it takes.
My Allah...
My Allah show me the way.
Alcicek!
Aktemur!
-Alcicek.
-Aktemur.
Alcicek?
Alcicek.
You're okay.
Are you okay?
Aktemur.
My baby.
Baby...
Kumral Abdal!
Kumral Abdal!!!
You're okay.
Okay.
Our baby is okay too.
Mother!
Kumral Abdal, come.
Mother Bengi!
Aktemur!
Alcicek!
Tell me she's alive, son.
She's alive thank Allah.
She's alive. Thank Allah. Thank Allah.
Come on.
My baby.
Alcicek.
Is she okay?
Aunt..
Alcicek!
Daughter.
Thank Allah. Thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
She's okay, she's okay.
But we need to go to Yenisehir quickly.
Come on.
- Come on.
-Alps bring the horses at once!
Get up.
Come on daughter.
Thank God the armies will arrive.
We will get rid of the Turks for good.
You should thank God, my friend Milos..
Once the armies are here..
I will be working with the devil.
Byzantine...
...owes you commanders a lot.
When you lead the armies...
..Turks will be banished from everywhere
Konya included.
Once the other armies join us...
...the Muslims will be done forever!
Are you looking for us?
Good job, boys.
Good job.
They're skilled, my Bey.
Of course they are.
It's going to be much worse over there,
my sons.
Even the slightest sound
might cause us our lives.
So be quiet.
The armies will be here.
I'll march on Yenisehir and Sogut.
You will take Inegol and
Bilecik with your armies.
-Commander Mateus.
-Yes, sir?
You will set
the remaining tribes on fire!
After all, you have experience
regarding the matter.
You're much more experienced
when it comes to killing Turks.
The armies will be victorious
under your command.
My sons.
...that's our target.
Take a good look at him.
Orhan.
Alaeddin.
You will take down the one on the right.
You will shoot two arrows
and finish them both at once.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Take the one on the left..
...and I'll take the one in the middle.
We'll attack them as one.
Let's go.
May Allah bless our War.
Ameen, my Bey.
Go now.
What are you doing here?
Osman.
You didn't expect to see me, did you?
I will kill you now.
It's over!
How did you find me?
I tried to think like you.
I taught myself how to think like you.
I told you not to mistake me for others.
I know about every step you take.
I know you, Osman.
Get out of here, sons.
We won't leave you, father.
Get out of here!
Come on.
Let's go
Oh, Haqq!
Go with them, Boran.
I won't leave you, my Bey.
-I won't you, my Bey.
- Boran!
-Boran!
-We can do it, my Bey.
Your sons will run,
we'll go after them.
We'll do it together, my Bey.
I'll cover you, my Bey.
Go!
Now!
My Bey!
My Bey, are you okay?
I am okay, this is nothing!
We went through worse!
You will see Valens!
Stop resisting, Osman!
Your beloved sons...
...will die in my hands!
And don't walk near the trees.
There are traps I prepared
for you in the forest!
Just because I did not spill your blood,
you act this way!
You can speak so highly because of that!
I am going to bury you
in the middle of Bursa’
Kill them!
I will come for you!
You will not be able to leave, Osman!
You will all die in this forest!
Boran!
Come on my Bey!
Where is the dungeon?
I can’t say.
If you have a request, tell me,
I will speak to Malhun Hatun.
Do you know who you are talking to?
I do not take anyone’s permission.
Tell me where the dungeon is.
I have questions for Ismihan.
He is doing his duty.
But...
...you don’t know where you stand, Hatun.
This is my mansion, watch your mouth here!
I am responsible for those in the dungeon,
Malhun Hatun.
And it's my duty to question them.
Now show me where the dungeon is.
I have things to talk with Ismihan.
Don't confuse me with anyone else, Hatun.
You have no power here.
You can't order me.
I will never allow you to
speak alone with Ismihan.
Gorkluce, bring the prisoners here.
Whatever you want to speak with her,
you will speak in front of me.
Don't you trust me, Malhun Hatun?
This is the borderlands, Hatun.
We learned that we shouldn't trust
anyone the hard way!
You brought this upon us due to your arrogance, mother.
You ruined us just to take revenge from Bengi!
Come on, get ready.
Where are we going?
I saved Osman Bey's life.
And you are still not trusting me,
Malhun Hatun?
I hope you are doing this
out of your responsibility to the state.
If it’s out of arrogance,
it is Ismihan who is the most arrogant one!
And her punishment is obvious!
We will take our precaution.
...you may think of us as arrogant.
There is no need to hurry, Hatun.
When we find Alcicek..
..we will give Ismihan
and Alaeddin to you.
Prepare the infirmary immediately!
Prepare the infirmary!
Call The Dark Midwife!
Aktemur, is she okay?
Thank Allah, aunt,
she will get better.
Come on, carry her.
Ulgen!
Bring hot water and clean towels!
Come on!
Beng,
-She's fine.
-She will get better.
Bengi Hatun!
Isn't she dead?
She's almost dead.
Good.
She'll die right in front of her mother.
What are you saying?
It's over. I killed her.
Then..
I will kill you Bengi Hatun.
Ismihan.
Ismihan I'll kill you.
Ismihan!
Bengi!
Enough!
She'll live.
Because she has loved ones.
We pray for her.
She's not like you Ismihan.
But you..
...your fate is clear.
You'll rot in a dungeon.
Bengi.
Alcicek's inside.
Go to her.
Go on.
Esrigun Hatun.
You can have her now.
Prepare the carriages.
Come on Alps!
Take her.
This won't end here.
I will be back.
Wait for that day.
Aral.
Be cautious.
Make sure the caravan's protected.
They will go to Gazan Khan
in one piece.
Be careful. I don't want problems.
What is it Esrigun Hatun?
What do you mean "they"?
Won't you go with them?
No.
I won't Malhun Hatun.
I didn’t know what this place was like.
The borders are in chaos.
Fixing this...
...is my job.
My Bey!
My Bey.
Sons. Sons... Boran.
My sons.
They're okay. They're running.
-Where are my sons?
-They're escaping.
They’re okay My Bey. Don't worry.
Are you okay my Bey?
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Valens. Valens.
Valens.
My sons.
We ran out of arrows.
We won't stop until we find my sons.
We won't my Bey.
We won't.
Don't let them get away.
I want Osman dead.
I want his sons dead.
You can't get away.
Come on.
They’re coming brother.
Hide Alaeddin. Hide.
Let them come. Let them come.
Alaeddin, on my mark.
Now.
Come on.
This way.
Alaeddin it's a trap don’t get up.
Come on. Come on.
I won't wait anymore.
I am going.
Hold on son, wait. Be a little patient.
I don’t have any left mother, I’m going in.
Dark Midwife!
Aktemur calm down.
Dark Midwife.
Dark Midwife!
Say something, is everything okay?
Alcicek is okay.
How about the baby?
Is the baby okay?
Tell us? Is the baby okay?
Ayse Hatun.
...how long were yo pregnant with him?
If he's like this now...
...what will he do
when the baby comes?
Thank Allah.
Ulgen.
Go and tell the alps.
We'll sacrifice an animal.
Dark Midwife!
How are they? Say something.
What does this mean?
Come on son..
...both your hatun and baby are okay.
The wound wasn't very deep, you are lucky.
Go and see your hatun then.
Dark Midwife!
You gave me such good news,
ask anything you want from me.
-May Allah bless you!
-Go in now. Go.
Thank you so much.
So, Bengi...
We went through one more hardship
together, huh?
Thank Allah.
Brother.
Hold on. Hold on.
Those merciless..
Those lowlife dogs...
Hold on.
Are you okay?
Are you?
I'm okay my Bey.
Brother.
Are you okay brother?
What will we do now brother?
We will use those practices we had.
Brother they're coming.
Come on Alaeddin. Come on.
Sons..
Brother... Sons..
Brother stop.
Stop. It's a trap.
Be careful.
They put traps everywhere.
The hunt is about to become the prey.
Come on.
Just like how father taught.
Oh, Haqq!
Let's go
Over there!
My sons.
We're going to find them, my Bey.
Let's get up.
Let's go.
We will not let them get away!
This will end!
I will stick Osman's head on the
edge of my sword!
Allah forbid,
what if they're in trouble, my Bey?
Sons.
My sons.
My sons...
Father!
Orhan.
Alaeddin.
Nayman!
Valens!
It's the end, Osman.
Your head will drop on the ground.
No.
You and your sons will die here,
Osman
Someone will pick up the flag after you, Osman.
But once all of you are dead...
...your names will be forgotten!
Let me tell you what's going to
happen after you die.
We will slaughter everyone!
...first in Yenisehir, then on all of your lands’!
I will retrieve everything you stole from Byzantium
The last thing you'll see on this world...
...will be the heads of your dead sons.
If you dare spill their blood...
..I will bury all of you here.
Now...
...let my sons go...
..and take me instead.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com